Guide to the Barbara Guest Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1940-2006; Series I
  - General correspondence
    - Guston, Philip, 1974 December 20 (Box 17, Folder 329)
    - "G" General (Box 17, Folder 330)
    - Hackett-Freedman Gallery, 1998 August 3–1998 September 12 (Box 17, Folder 331)
    - Haden-Guest, Elissa, 2004 April 17–2006 April 10 (Box 17, Folder 332)
    - Haden-Guest, Hadley, 1966 December 1–1979 December 19 (Box 17, Folder 333)
    - Haden-Guest, Peter, 1984 June 21 (Box 17, Folder 334)
    - Hagen-Stubbing, Yvonne, 2003-03-27- (Box 17, Folder 335)
    - Halman, Talat S., 1971 December 3 (Box 17, Folder 336)
    - Hambone, 1989 February 21–1989 April 11 (Box 17, Folder 337)
    - Handley, Helen, 1984 November 11 (Box 17, Folder 338)
    - Hannan, Jack, 1978 September 27–1983 November 28 (Box 17, Folder 339)
    - HarperCollins Publishers, 1992 March 9 (Box 17, Folder 340)
    - Harris, Carolyn, 1996 November 27 (Box 17, Folder 341)
    - Hartigan, Grace, 1958 July 21–1976 March 10 (Box 17, Folder 342)
    - Hasler, Paul, 1958 August 20 (Box 18, Folder 343)
    - Hass, Robert, 2003 May 12–2005 February 27 (Box 18, Folder 344)
    - Haven, Cynthia, 2006 February 16–2006 February 18 (Box 18, Folder 345)
    - Hawley, Anthony, 2005 November 20–2006 February 20 (Box 18, Folder 346)
    - Hechinger, Fred, 1980 January 12 (Box 18, Folder 347)
    - Hejinian, Lyn, 1979 October 14–1994 June 20 (Box 18, Folder 348)
    - Heliczer, Piero, 1975 November 30 (Box 18, Folder 349)
    - Hesselberg, Gregory, 1984 July 13–1988 February 17 (Box 18, Folder 350)
    - Hesselholdt, Christina, 1993 March 22–1993 June (Box 18, Folder 351)
    - Heyday Books, 2004 January 6–2005 January 7 (Box 18, Folder 352)
    - Heydt, Erich, 1984 August 15 (Box 18, Folder 353)
    - Hickman, Leland, 1987 May 30–1989 April 5 (Box 18, Folder 354)
    - Higgins, Jonathan, 2002-12- (Box 18, Folder 355)
    - Higgins, Trumbull, 1957 June 2–1957 June 14 (Box 18, Folder 356)
    - Hillman, Brenda, 1995 August 19–2006 February 21 (Box 18, Folder 357)
    - Hillringhouse, Mark, 1991 May 28–1996 June 25 (Box 18, Folder 358)
    - Hilton, Jeremy, 2004 January 23–2006 May 10 (Box 18, Folder 359)
    - Hine, Hank, 1990-07-21-1992-08-03 (Box 18, Folder 360)
    - Hirschl & Adler, 1986 April 25 (Box 18, Folder 361)
    - Hodspith, Vicki, 1997 May 6 (Box 18, Folder 362)
    - Hogue, Cynthia, 2003 May 6-2006 February 23 (Box 18, Folder 363)
    - Hollenberg, Donna, 1994 October 4 (Box 18, Folder 364)
    - Holman, Bob, 2004 January 26–2005 January 17 (Box 18, Folder 365)
    - Honrath, Barbara, 1989 October 20-2003 July 9 (Box 18, Folder 366-367)
    - Hoover Institute, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 368)
    - Hoover, Paul, 1992 July 23–1992 August 26 (Box 19, Folder 369)
    - Hopkins, Kenneth, 1980 February 18 (Box 19, Folder 370)
    - Horovitz, Michael, 1970-09-21- (Box 19, Folder 371)
    - Houghton Mifflin Company, 1983 May 31 (Box 19, Folder 372)
    - Housen, Al, undated (Box 19, Folder 373)
    - Howard Foundation, 1997 September 30–1998 September 24 (Box 19, Folder 374)
    - Howard, Richard, 1977 September 13 (Box 19, Folder 375)
    - Howe, Fanny, 2005-03-11- (Box 19, Folder 376)
    - Howe, Susan, 1976 November 7–1994 January 31 (Box 19, Folder 377)
    - "H" General (Box 19, Folder 378)
    - Iijima, Brenda, 2005 April 17 (Box 19, Folder 379)
    - Institute of American Indian Arts Press, 1985 February 6 (Box 19, Folder 380)
    - Interiors, 1984 September (Box 19, Folder 381)
    - International Biographical Centre, 1997 February 21 (Box 19, Folder 382)
    - International Exhibitions Foundation, 1984 November 20–1986 November 21 (Box 19, Folder 383)
    - Iowa Review, 1985 July 3–1996 May 30 (Box 19, Folder 384)
    - Ironwood, 1984 February 27–1987 June 24 (Box 19, Folder 385)
    - Isham, Heyward, 1993 February 28 (Box 19, Folder 386)
    - Isham, Sheila, 1973 March 7-2004 April 13 (Box 19, Folder 387)
    - Istituto Italiano di Cultura, 1964 April 30 (Box 19, Folder 388)
    - Jack Kerouac School of Disembodied Poetics, 1995 March 16 (Box 19, Folder 389)
    - Jacket Magazine, 1999 November 10–2006 February 18 (Box 20, Folder 390)
    - Jackson, Laura, 1964 February 13–1984 March 10 (Box 20, Folder 391)
    - Jacobs, Jonathan L., 1993 December 1 (Box 20, Folder 392)
    - Jacobson, Aileen, undated (Box 20, Folder 393)
    - Jaffe, James S., 1991 February 20–2002 November 6 (Box 20, Folder 394)
    - Jaffer, Frances, 1981 October 1 (Box 20, Folder 395)
    - Janis, Sidney, undated (Box 20, Folder 396)
    - John Jay College of Criminal Justice, 1992 May 26 (Box 20, Folder 397)
    - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1984 July 6 (Box 20, Folder 398)
    - Johnson, Buffie, 1984 August 27 (Box 20, Folder 399)
    - Johnson, Evelyn, 1969 August 15 (Box 20, Folder 400)
    - Johnson, Nicholas, 1996 April 10–1997 June 19 (Box 20, Folder 401)
    - Jolas, Maria, 1966 June 11 (Box 20, Folder 402)
    - Jones, Alice, undated (Box 20, Folder 403)
    - Jones, Steve, 1986 November 20 (Box 20, Folder 404)
    - Jordan, Barbara Scott, 1980 March 3 (Box 20, Folder 405)
    - Joron, Andrew, 1994 October 22–2006 June 6 (Box 20, Folder 406)
    - Joseph the Provider, 1985 August 26 (Box 20, Folder 407)
    - Journal 1913, 2003 October 11–2004 September 28 (Box 20, Folder 408)
    - "J" General (Box 20, Folder 409)
    - Kasper, Catherine L., 1996 October 8–2006 May 10 (Box 20, Folder 410)
    - Kaufman, Rob, 1995 May 27–2006 June 29 (Box 20, Folder 411)
    - Kazin, Alfred, 1984 September 10 (Box 21, Folder 412)
    - Kelleher, Carl, 2004 November 9–2004 November 29 (Box 21, Folder 413)
    - Keller, Lynn, 1996 February 13–1997 May 28 (Box 21, Folder 414)
    - Kelley, Andrew, 2003 October 23 (Box 21, Folder 415)
    - Kelmslie, Kenward, 1999 February 21–1999 April 19 (Box 21, Folder 416)
    - Kelsey Street Press, 1987 January 27-2006 February 19 (Box 21, Folder 417-418)
    - Kenyon Review, 2004 January 12 (Box 21, Folder 419)
    - Kermani, David, 1976 December 12 (Box 21, Folder 420)
    - Kernan, Nathan, 1995 October 30–1996 November 14 (Box 21, Folder 421)
    - Kessler, Jascha, 1962 October 20–1979 July 19 (Box 21, Folder 422)
    - Ketcham, Diana, 1991 May 25 (Box 21, Folder 423)
    - Killian, Kevin, 1995 April 26–2006 June 28 (Box 21, Folder 424)
    - King, Basil, 2002 August 23 (Box 21, Folder 425)
    - King, Michael, 1985 October–1985 December 11 (Box 21, Folder 426)
    - Kingershot, Julie, 1998 June 21 (Box 21, Folder 427)
    - Koch, Karen, 2006 March 9 (Box 21, Folder 428)
    - Koch, Kenneth, 1960 May 13–1990 May 15 (Box 21, Folder 429)
    - Kot, Richard P., 1987 November 12 (Box 21, Folder 430)
    - KPFA FM 94.1, 1992 December 8–1996 March 21 (Box 21, Folder 431)
    - Kuhl, Nancy, 2004 December 24–2006 July 10 (Box 21, Folder 432)
    - Kwan, John Y., 1998 September 18 (Box 21, Folder 433)
    - "K" General (Box 21, Folder 434)
    - Lally, Michael, 1990 September 13 (Box 22, Folder 435)
    - Lamerdin, Pat, 1987 September 12 (Box 22, Folder 436)
    - Langland, Joseph, undated (Box 22, Folder 437)
    - Lannan Foundation, 1995 May 8–1996 April 23 (Box 22, Folder 438-439)
    - Lansner, Fay, 1964-07-10-1990-05-22 (Box 22, Folder 440)
    - Lansner, Gabrielle, 2005 January 3–2005 November 9 (Box 22, Folder 441)
    - Lapis Press, 1987 March 2–1987 March 31 (Box 22, Folder 442)
    - Larkin, Mary Rose, 1996 December 4–2006 June 27 (Box 22, Folder 443)
    - Lauer, Brett, 2001 December 31–2006 July 9 (Box 22, Folder 444)
    - Laughlin, James, 1959 May 21–1987 August 13 (Box 22, Folder 445)
    - Laurence Pollinger Limited, 1984 June 19–1985 August 14 (Box 22, Folder 446)
    - Lauterbach, Ann, 1950 April 28–2006 July 1 (Box 22, Folder 447)
    - Law, Ann, 1954 December 1-2005 March 29 (Box 22, Folder 448)
    - Law, G. D., 1956 January 9 (Box 22, Folder 449)
    - Lee, Annabel, 2006-03-17- (Box 22, Folder 450)
    - Lehman, David, 1988 February 8–2006 July 2 (Box 22, Folder 451)
    - Lerner, Ben, 2003 March 16–2004 March 25 (Box 22, Folder 452)
    - Leslie, Alfred, 1959 September 1 (Box 23, Folder 453)
    - Leslie, Davis, 1981 June 13 (Box 23, Folder 454)
    - Lethbridge, Sheila Powell, 2002 December 30 (Box 23, Folder 455)
    - LeVasser, Christine, 2004 June 23–2004 June 29 (Box 23, Folder 456)
    - Levitt, Annabel, 1977 November 2–1999 February 15 (Box 23, Folder 457)
    - Library of Congress, 1960 November 18–1996 November 16 (Box 23, Folder 458)
    - Library of the Society of the Four Arts, 1984 November 16 (Box 23, Folder 459)
    - Lifson, Martha, 1988 February 29 (Box 23, Folder 460)
    - Lindley, Denver, 1951 July 16 (Box 23, Folder 461)
    - LINEbreak, 1995 December 16 (Box 23, Folder 462)
    - LINES, undated (Box 23, Folder 463)
    - Linick, Anthony, 1963 October 17–1963 November 6 (Box 23, Folder 464)
    - Linklater, Andro, 1982 December 8 (Box 23, Folder 465)
    - Liste, Karen Hagen, 2003 May 2-2006 June 5 (Box 23, Folder 466)
    - Literary Review, 2004 June 10–2004 August 24 (Box 23, Folder 467)
    - Litz, Theresa, 2001 August 28 (Box 23, Folder 468)
    - Long Island University, 1990 May 11–1993 February 9 (Box 23, Folder 469)
    - Long, Robert, 1989 September 30–2006 February 23 (Box 23, Folder 470)
    - Longview Foundation, 1961 February 2 (Box 23, Folder 471)
    - Longville, Tim, 1984 July 16–1989 December 12 (Box 23, Folder 472)
    - Los Angeles County Museum of Art, 1994 January 11 (Box 23, Folder 473)
    - Low, Barbara, 1953 September 24 (Box 23, Folder 474)
    - Low, Jackson Mac, 2002 September 13 (Box 23, Folder 475)
    - Lowell, Robert, 1966 March 24 (Box 23, Folder 476)
    - Lucas, Brian, 2003 June 9–2005 April 30 (Box 23, Folder 477)
    - Ludman, Joan, 1991 April 12 (Box 23, Folder 478)
    - Lundquist, Sara, 1995 September 6–2006 February 25 (Box 23, Folder 479)
    - Lungfull Magazine, 2005 June 20–2005 October 3 (Box 24, Folder 480)
    - Lyons, Kim, undated (Box 24, Folder 481)
    - "L" General (Box 24, Folder 482)
    - Mac Low, Jackson, 1964 February 10 (Box 24, Folder 483)
    - MacCarthy, Desmond, 1974 January 10 (Box 24, Folder 484)
    - Mackenzie, Michael, 1974 April 11 (Box 24, Folder 485)
    - Malanga, Gerard, 1962 July 26–1975 January 10 (Box 24, Folder 486)
    - Manifest Press, 2000 February 11 (Box 24, Folder 487)
    - Manousos, Anthony, 1979 August 28–1979 October 17 (Box 24, Folder 488)
    - Mansfield Book Mart Ltd., 1980 February 29 (Box 24, Folder 489)
    - Marcincuk, Mary S., 2003 May 17 (Box 24, Folder 490)
    - Marie Rodell–Frances Collin Literary Agency, 1980 November 20 (Box 24, Folder 491)
    - Marks, Charles E., 1969 April 10–2005 February 3 (Box 24, Folder 492)
    - Marlowe, Alan S., 1964 October 10–1965 February 15 (Box 24, Folder 493)
    - Marquis Who's Who, 2004 August 24 (Box 24, Folder 494)
    - Marshall, Lenore G., 1967 June 12–1967 June 13 (Box 24, Folder 495)
    - Martha Jackson Gallery, 1961 March 8 (Box 24, Folder 496)
    - Martin, John, undated (Box 24, Folder 497)
    - Masand, Aroon, 2003 July 17 (Box 24, Folder 498)
    - Maso, Carole, 1977 February 9 (Box 24, Folder 499)
    - Mathews, Harry B., 1962 May 1–2005 February 23 (Box 24, Folder 500)
    - Mathias, Jim F., 1984 January 17 (Box 24, Folder 501)
    - Maxwell, Andrew, 2001 July 18-2003 March 31 (Box 24, Folder 502)
    - Mayer, Bernadette, 1979 November 19–1980 January 27 (Box 24, Folder 503)
    - Mayer, Jed, 2003 May 11–2005 May 20 (Box 24, Folder 504)
    - McCurdy, Charles G., 2002 September 11 (Box 24, Folder 505)
    - McDarrah, Fred, 1960 May 20 (Box 24, Folder 506)
    - McKeon, June, 2001 August 30 (Box 24, Folder 507)
    - McQuade, Molly, 1998 February 1 (Box 24, Folder 508)
    - Mears, Carol Selph, 2004 September 9–2006 March 14 (Box 24, Folder 509)
    - Medina, Kate, undated (Box 24, Folder 510)
    - Merchant, Yolanda, 2006 June 11–2006 June 30 (Box 24, Folder 511)
    - Merwin, William, 1961 March 9–1961 October 26 (Box 24, Folder 512)
    - Messerli, Douglas, 1993 August 17–2005 April 4 (Box 24, Folder 513)
    - Meyer, Tom, 2004 May 1–2004 May 3 (Box 24, Folder 514)
    - Miami University, 1991 November 6–1996 May 10 (Box 24, Folder 515)
    - Milici, John A., 1995 June 6 (Box 25, Folder 516)
    - Millburn, Nancy and George, 2004 December 27–2005 August 30 (Box 25, Folder 517)
    - Miller, Robert, 1987 May 27 (Box 25, Folder 518)
    - Miller, Sandra, 2006 March 15 (Box 25, Folder 519)
    - Mills College, 1998 October 17–2004 March 3 (Box 25, Folder 520)
    - Mississippi Review, 1990 December 11 (Box 25, Folder 521)
    - Mitchell, Joan, 1959 October 19–1968 June 23 (Box 25, Folder 522)
    - Montague, John, 1966 August (Box 25, Folder 523)
    - Montemora Foundation, 1978 November 6–1978 November 11 (Box 25, Folder 524)
    - Moore College of Art, 1977 May 23–1978 January 23 (Box 25, Folder 525)
    - Moore, Harry T., 1978 October 25 (Box 25, Folder 526)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1963 March 8 (Box 25, Folder 527)
    - Moorman, Jane C., 2000 March 10–2005 January 20 (Box 25, Folder 528)
    - Moorman, Priscilla C., 2002-01-07-2002-12-26 (Box 25, Folder 529)
    - Moravian College, 1986 July 9 (Box 25, Folder 530)
    - More, Michael, 1997 March 7 (Box 25, Folder 531)
    - Morgan, Bill, 1985 February 13 (Box 25, Folder 532)
    - Morley, Hilda, 1982 August 2 (Box 25, Folder 533)
    - Morrel, Harriet, 1960 June 8 (Box 25, Folder 534)
    - Morris, Ina, 1965 May 31-1971 March 22 (Box 25, Folder 535)
    - Morrison, Rusty, 2004 March 5 (Box 25, Folder 536)
    - Morrow, Bradford, 1984 March 21–1996 September 6 (Box 25, Folder 537)
    - Morse, Carl, 1964 June 22–1964 June 27 (Box 25, Folder 538)
    - Moss, Howard, 1964 February 11 (Box 25, Folder 539)
    - Moss, Stanley, 1985 January 2 (Box 25, Folder 540)
    - MOTHER, 1965 March 10 (Box 25, Folder 541)
    - Motherwell, Robert, 1982 August 9–1983 August 9 (Box 25, Folder 542)
    - Mottram, Eric, 1973 September 4–1988 March 31 (Box 25, Folder 543)
    - Mount Holyoke College Art Museum, 1988 September 30–1988 October 5 (Box 25, Folder 544)
    - Moynihan, Daniel P., 1973 November 12 (Box 25, Folder 545)
    - Moynihan, Rodrigo, 1966 December 6–1966 December 14 (Box 25, Folder 546)
    - Mueller, Robert, 1995 April 7–2006 March 8 (Box 26, Folder 548)
    - Murmur Magazine, 2001 June 7 (Box 26, Folder 549)
    - Murphy, Ryan, 2004 October 10–2006 February 6 (Box 26, Folder 550)
    - Museum of Modern Art, 1973 March 21–2002 March 8 (Box 26, Folder 551)
    - Myers, John, 1960 January 28–1973 July 31 (Box 26, Folder 552)
    - Myles, Eileen, 1977 March 27–1977 April 11 (Box 26, Folder 553)
    - "M" General (Box 26, Folder 554)
    - Naropa Institute, 1994 November 27–1998 July 14 (Box 26, Folder 555)
    - Naropa University, 2003 July 31–2005 November 5 (Box 26, Folder 556)
    - National Collection of Fine Arts, 1972 February 8 (Box 26, Folder 557)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1979 September 26 (Box 26, Folder 558)
    - National Poetry Foundation, 1985 February 13–1999 October 1 (Box 26, Folder 559)
    - National Poetry Series, 1994 June 28 (Box 26, Folder 560)
    - Negosanu, Petronela, 1970 July 17–1980 December (Box 26, Folder 561)
    - Neilsen, Karla, 2002 August 5–2003 March 6 (Box 26, Folder 562)
    - Nelson, Gale, 1989 December 8–2003 December 23 (Box 26, Folder 563)
    - New American Writing, 1990 December 23–1995 February 24 (Box 26, Folder 564)
    - New College of California, 1995 November 14–1998 November 24 (Box 27, Folder 565)
    - New Fiction Writing, undated (Box 27, Folder 566)
    - Newgarden, Albert, 1990 March 25 (Box 27, Folder 567)
    - New Review of Literature, 2003 December 10–2005 August 17 (Box 27, Folder 568)
    - New School for Social Research, undated (Box 27, Folder 569)
    - New Student Review, 1964 September 29 (Box 27, Folder 570)
    - New Yorker, 1956 June 8 (Box 27, Folder 571)
    - New York Public Library, 1965 March 1 (Box 27, Folder 572)
    - New York State, 1993 April 1 (Box 27, Folder 573)
      Includes photographs of Guest's living space interiors
    - New York University, 1964 December 4–1992 August 31 (Box 27, Folder 574)
    - Niccolai, Giulia, 1999 March 24–1999 September 29 (Box 27, Folder 575)
    - No Journal, 2002 June 13-2006 February 21 (Box 27, Folder 576)
    - No Roses Review, 1995 August 23–1995 September 18 (Box 27, Folder 577)
    - North, Charles, 1978 January 14–2006 February 27 (Box 27, Folder 578)
    - Northwest, undated (Box 27, Folder 579)
    - "N" General (Box 27, Folder 580)
    - Oblek, 1987 October 3–1991 January 22 (Box 27, Folder 581)
    - Occidental College, 1990 October 2 (Box 27, Folder 582)
    - Octopus Magazine, 2004 January 17–2005 May 15 (Box 27, Folder 583)
    - Oferio, George, undated (Box 27, Folder 584)
    - O'Hara, Frank, 1952 May 23-1959 July 6 (Box 27, Folder 585)
    - Oink!, 1986 May 14 (Box 27, Folder 586)
    - Oliver, Laura, 1997 October 19 (Box 27, Folder 587)
    - Olson, Charles, 1957 November 28–1966 February 7 (Box 27, Folder 588)
    - Orwell, Sonia, 1968 November 22–1969 March 24 (Box 27, Folder 589)
    - Osborne Travel Bureau, 1987 October 17 (Box 27, Folder 590)
    - Osman, Jena, 1994-08-28- (Box 27, Folder 591)
    - O'Sullivan, Maggie, 1994 October 20–1996 August 13 (Box 28, Folder 592)
    - Oxford University Press, 2005 December 14–2006 July 2 (Box 28, Folder 593)
    - Owens, Rochelle, 1990 January 22 (Box 28, Folder 594)
    - Ozawa, Melissa, 2002 April 15 (Box 28, Folder 595)
    - Ozment, Kurt, 2003 March 2 (Box 28, Folder 596)
    - "O" General (Box 28, Folder 597)
    - Pace University, 1997 July 20 (Box 28, Folder 598)
    - Pacific Switchboard, 2004 March 18 (Box 28, Folder 599)
    - Padgett, Ron, 1966 June 7–1979 May 28 (Box 28, Folder 600)
    - Paideuma, 1984 February 17–1985 December 3 (Box 28, Folder 601)
    - Palmer, Michael, 1999 August 23 (Box 28, Folder 602)
    - Paris, Jean, 1957 May 10–1960 November 27 (Box 28, Folder 603)
    - Paris Press, 2004 April 23–2004 August 5 (Box 28, Folder 604)
    - Paris Review, 1967 May 21 (Box 28, Folder 605)
    - Parrish Art Museum, 1998 April 9-20 (Box 28, Folder 606)
    - Pelzel, John, 1951 April 19–1971 May 21 (Box 28, Folder 607)
    - Pembroke Magazine, 1988 September 23–1988 October 11 (Box 28, Folder 608)
    - PEN Center USA West, 1996 May 22 (Box 28, Folder 609)
    - Penguin Books Ltd., 1966 July 6 (Box 28, Folder 610)
    - Penguin USA, 1991 April 19–2004 December 6 (Box 28, Folder 611)
    - Pennant, Edward, 1989 October 9 (Box 28, Folder 612)
    - Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts, 1985 March 29 (Box 28, Folder 613)
    - Pennsylvania Humanities Council, 1984 October 3–1985 January 9 (Box 28, Folder 614)
    - Percival, Willa, 1957 June 21 (Box 28, Folder 615)
    - Pereira, Maria José, 2003 March 6–2006 March 6 (Box 28, Folder 616)
    - Perelman, Bob, 1999 August 27 (Box 28, Folder 617)
    - Perloff, Marjorie, 1997 July 19 (Box 28, Folder 618)
    - Permanent Press, 1985 July 2–1985 September 10 (Box 28, Folder 619)
    - Perril, Simon, undated (Box 28, Folder 620)
    - Phelan, Kevin P. Q., 2001 July 8 (Box 28, Folder 621)
    - Philip, Sonya, 2003 May 29 (Box 28, Folder 622)
    - Phillips, Dennis, 1987 May 5–2005 December 20 (Box 28, Folder 623)
    - Phillips, Jimmy, 1962 October 25 (Box 28, Folder 624)
    - Pinson, Anna Mae, 1950 February 20–1957 June 4 (Box 28, Folder 625)
    - Pinson, David and Cathy, 1984 July 5 (Box 28, Folder 626)
    - Pinson, Lori, 2002 June 10–2004 August 18 (Box 28, Folder 627)
    - Pinson, Mark, 2006 February 20 (Box 28, Folder 628)
    - Planz, Allen, 1967 November 1 (Box 28, Folder 629)
    - Pleynet, Marcelin, 1965 September 28 (Box 28, Folder 630)
    - Poesis, 1984 November 14–1985 November 6 (Box 29, Folder 631)
    - Poetry Book Society, 1961 November 20 (Box 29, Folder 632)
    - Poetry Canada Review, 1989 February 10 (Box 29, Folder 633)
    - Poetry Center, 1978 December 4–1991 October 22 (Box 29, Folder 634)
    - Poetry Literary Magazine, 1961 April 21–1963 December 2 (Box 29, Folder 635)
    - Poetry Project, 1967 September 15–2003 June 12 (Box 29, Folder 636)
    - Poetry Society of America, 1979 November 8–2006 June 28 (Box 29, Folder 637)
    - Poets & Writers, undated (Box 29, Folder 638)
    - Poets for Choice at Ceres, undated (Box 29, Folder 639)
    - Poets House, 1987 July 20–1992 August 6 (Box 29, Folder 640)
    - Poindexter Gallery, undated (Box 29, Folder 641)
    - Porter, Anne E., 1994 May 31–2006 June 2 (Box 29, Folder 642)
    - Porter, Fairfield, 1955 August 23–1966 July 10 (Box 29, Folder 643)
    - Post-Apollo Press, 1996 October 6–2004 November 8 (Box 29, Folder 644)
    - Poulson Gluck design, 2002 August 5 (Box 29, Folder 645)
    - Pound, Mary, 1981 November 20 (Box 29, Folder 646)
    - Powell, Anthony, 1981 April 3 (Box 29, Folder 647)
    - Powell, Russell E., 1948-1990 May 2 (Box 29, Folder 648-649)
    - Preston, David and Georgette, 1993 February 20–2005 January 31 (Box 29, Folder 650)
    - Pryce-Jones, Alan, 1985 November 1 (Box 29, Folder 651)
    - Prynne, Jeremy H., 1974 May 5–1976 January 29 (Box 30, Folder 652)
    - Pulse, 1998 September 15 (Box 30, Folder 653)
    - Pushcart Press, 1989 December 11 (Box 30, Folder 654)
    - "P" General (Box 30, Folder 655)
    - Quartermain, Meredith, 1999 July 6–2002 July 6 (Box 30, Folder 656)
    - Quartermain, Peter, 1996 September 30–1996 October 14 (Box 30, Folder 657)
    - Queens College, 1984 May 19–1984 August 9 (Box 30, Folder 658)
    - "Q" General (Box 30, Folder 659)
    - Rabinowitz, Anna, 1995 April 18–2005 March 6 (Box 30, Folder 660)
    - Radio France, 1976 July 29 (Box 30, Folder 661)
    - Rahv, Philip, 1951 September 9–1957 March 25 (Box 30, Folder 662)
    - Rain Taxi, 2004 May 21–2006 July 12 (Box 30, Folder 663)
    - Random House, 1994 May 12 (Box 30, Folder 664)
    - Rankine, Claudia, 2002 August 7 (Box 30, Folder 665)
    - Rasula, Jed, 1984 August 15 (Box 30, Folder 666)
    - Ratcliffe, Stephen, 2002 February 14–2005 November 21 (Box 30, Folder 667-669)
    - Rattray, David, 1985 March 26 (Box 31, Folder 670)
    - Raworth, Tom, 2004 December 13–2006 February 25 (Box 31, Folder 671)
    - Reality Street Editions, 1995 December 12–2006 July 3 (Box 31, Folder 672)
    - Redwoods, 1996 April 23 (Box 31, Folder 673)
    - Rehm, Pam, 1995 August 5 (Box 31, Folder 674)
    - Reid, Laurie, 1999 November 4–2004 February 8 (Box 31, Folder 675)
    - Retallack, Joan, 1997 January 16-1999 October 25 (Box 31, Folder 676)
    - Revell, Donald, 1990 March 9–1996 October 8 (Box 31, Folder 677)
    - Review of Contemporary Fiction, 1984 July 29 (Box 31, Folder 678)
    - Ribot, 1998 January 10 (Box 31, Folder 679)
    - Richard Seaver Books, 1973 July 30 (Box 31, Folder 680)
    - Rider, Josephine C., 1974 April 16 (Box 31, Folder 681)
    - Riding, Laura, 1964 February 7 (Box 31, Folder 682)
    - Riley, Peter, 1993 April 29-1998 February 28 (Box 31, Folder 683)
    - Ristorante Tor di Mezzavia, 1968 December 15 (Box 31, Folder 684)
    - Rivera, Elena, 2006 February 27 (Box 31, Folder 685)
    - Rivers, Larry, 1961 January 17 (Box 31, Folder 686)
    - Robbin, Nancy, 1957 May 21–2005 August 30 (Box 31, Folder 687)
    - Robert Cornfield Literary Agency, 1984 January–1990 May 18 (Box 31, Folder 688)
    - Robert Miller Gallery, 1981 January 23 (Box 31, Folder 689)
    - Robert O'Keene Bookshop & Gallery, 1959 October 2 (Box 31, Folder 690)
    - Robert, Warren, 1978 October 10 (Box 31, Folder 691)
    - Robinson, Elizabeth, 1987 January 25–1988 September 16 (Box 31, Folder 692)
    - Robinson, Jenny, 2006 February 28 (Box 31, Folder 693)
    - Rogow, Zack, 2004 May 25–2004 June 22 (Box 31, Folder 694)
    - Ronk, Martha, 1996 July 1–2005 January 22 (Box 31, Folder 695)
    - Rose Art Museum, 1981 February 9 (Box 31, Folder 696)